<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SBST 2020 on Search-Based Software Testing</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SBST 2020 on Search-Based Software Testing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SBST 2020</title>
      <link>/keynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/keynotes/</guid>
      <description>Keynote Speakers To be announced.   Tutorial Speaker Matias Martinez Université Polytechnique Hauts-de-France
Astor: A framework for building automated software repair approaches.
Abstract: Astor is a framework for building approaches that repair buggy Java programs. Those repair approaches take as input a buggy Java program (having at least one failing test case that exposes the bug) and search for a patch that produces all test cases to pass. Astor provides twelve extension points that form the design space of program repair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBST 2020</title>
      <link>/organisation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/organisation/</guid>
      <description> Co-Chairs Erik Fredericks Oakland University, USA
    Jos&amp;eacute; Miguel Rojas University of Leicester, UK
       Program Committee  Nazareno Aguirre, Universidad Nacional de Río Cuarto - CONICET, Argentina Giuliano Antoniol, Ecole Polytechnique de Montréal, Canada Jose Campos, University of Washington, USA John Clark, The University of Sheffield, UK Myra Cohen, Iowa State University, USA Byron DeVries, Grand Valley State University, USA Gordon Fraser, University of Passau, Germany Gregory Gay, Chalmers and the University of Gothenburg, Sweden Giovani Guizzo, University College London, UK Phil McMinn, The University of Sheffield, UK Sebastiano Panichella, University of Zurich, Switzerland Annibale Panichella, Delft University of Technology, Netherlands Justyna Petke, University College London, UK Paolo Tonella, Università della Svizzera Italiana, Switzerland Thomas Vogel, Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Germany Shin Yoo, Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology, Republic of Korea Jie Zhang, University College London, UK     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBST 2020</title>
      <link>/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/program/</guid>
      <description> Workshop Program  To be announced.      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBST 2020</title>
      <link>/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tools/</guid>
      <description>Tool Competition This year as well we are pleased to announce the eighth edition of the unit testing tool competition. We invite researchers to participate in the competition with their unit test generation tool for Java. Tools will be evaluated against a benchmark with respect to code coverage and mutation score. To participate:  notify the organizers by sending an email to Xavier Devroey, Sebastiano Panichela, and Alessio Gambi (x.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBST 2020</title>
      <link>/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/venue/</guid>
      <description>Venue SBST&#39;20 will be co-located with ICSE&#39;20 in Seoul, South Korea.
For more information on the venue, please visit https://conf.researchr.org/venue/icse-2020/icse-2020-venue.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>